A Guide to the Records of the Virginia State Board of Elections, Campaign Finance Division, Campaign Expense Accounts, 1992-2007
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Records of the Virginia State Board of Elections, Campaign Finance Division, Campaign Expense Accounts1992-2007
The Library of Virginia
44898
30 cu. ft.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Virginia State Board of Elections, Campaign Finance Division, Nancy Rodrigues, 1100 Bank Street, Richmond, VA 23216, transferred 14 April 2010 and accessioned 16 April 2010.
Historical Information
The State Board of Elections was created by an act of the General Assembly passed on March 26 1946. The act granted the board supervisory powers earlier exercised by the secretary of the commonwealth and the Board of State Canvassers over elections. The primary functions of the State Board of Elections are to supervise and coordinate the work of county and city electoral boards and of registrars to obtain uniformity in election proceedings and legality in all elections.
The State Board of Elections consists of three members who are appointed by the Governor subject to confirmation by the General Assembly. A majority of the Board is appointed from the political party which cast the highest number of votes in the Commonwealth for Governor at the last preceding gubernatorial election. The regular term of office is four years, and no member of the Board except the secretary is eligible for more than two successive terms.
The Board issues rules and regulations to guide the work of the electoral boards and registrars. The Board is empowered to remove from office any election official who fails to discharge the duties of his office, and it may request assistance from the office of the Attorney General to enforce election laws or prosecute any violations.
The Board is also responsible for establishing and maintaining a central record-keeping system to provide a roster of all qualified voters in the Commonwealth by county or city and by the precincts within each county or city. The roster must be purged regularly to delete the names of disqualified voters.
Scope and Content
The Virginia State Board of Elections, Campaign Finance Division, Campaign Expense Reports, are housed in 30 box and are divided into four series. Series have been designated for: I. Political Action Committees (PACs), 2003-2007; II. Virginia House of Delegates, 1993-2005; III. Virginia State Senate, 1992-2003; and IV. Statewide, 2001 and 2005. These records consist of correspondence, and Fair Elections Practices Act (FEPA) reports, statements and forms, including reports of campaign contributions, itemization of contributions, itemization of expenditures, itemization of loans received and repaid, obligations remaining unpaid, and reports of receipts and expenditures for a candidate or committee supporting candidates for nomination or election to state office. The campaign expense accounts document the sources and amount of funding for all candidates running for office in Virginia. These accounts are divided into reports of individual candidates and reports of political action committees (PAC).
Candiate Expense Reports are available on-line at the State Board of Elections web site for all candidates for the Virginia General Assembly and for statewide office, beginning with the November 2001 general election. Political Action Committee Reports (PACs) are available on-line only for those political committees that e-file with the State Board of Elections.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
I. Political Action Committees (PACs), 2003-2007
II. Virginia House of Delegates, 1993-2005
III. Virginia State Senate, 1992-2003
IV. Statewide, 2001-2005
Contents List
- I. Political Action Committees (PACs), 2003-2007., Extent: 21 cubic feet (21 boxes). (Box 1-21)
  Series is arranged alphabetically with political party committees first.
  - Virginia State Legislative Black Caucus, 2003-2007 (Box 1)
  - Virginia Senate Democratic Caucus, 2003-2007 (Box 1)
  - House Democratic Caucus, 2003-2007 (Box 1)
  - Democratic Legislative Campaign Caucus, 2003-2007 (Box 1)
  - 1st Congressional District Democratic Party, 2003-2007 (Box 1)
  - 2nd Congressional District Democratic Party, 2003-2007 (Box 1)
  - 3rd Congressional District Democratic Party, 2003-2007 (Box 1)
  - 4th Congressional District Democratic Party, 2003-2007 (Box 1)
  - 5th Congressional District Democratic Party, 2003-2007 (Box 1)
  - 6th Congressional District Democratic Party, 2003-2007 (Box 1)
  - 7th Congressional District Democratic Party, 2003-2007 (Box 1)
  - 8th Congressional District Democratic Party, 2003-2007 (Box 1)
  - 9th Congressional District Democratic Party, 2003-2007 (Box 1)
  - 10th Congressional District Democratic Party, 2003-2007 (Box 1)
  - 21st Century Democrats, 2003-2007 (Box 1)
  - Commonwealth Victory Fund, 2003-2007 (Box 1)
  - Albemarle County Democratic Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 1)
  - Albemarle Charlottesville Democratic Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 1)
  - Alexandria Democratic Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 1)
  - Charlottesville Democratic Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 1)
  - Democratic Legislative Black Caucus, 2003-2007 (Box 1)
  - Democratic Club of Metro Richmond, 2003-2007 (Box 1)
  - Democratic Party of Virginia, 2003-2007 (Box 1)
  - Dranesville District Democratic Party, 2003-2007 (Box 1)
  - Fairfax County Democratic Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 1)
  - Fauquier County Democratic Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 1)
  - Hampton Democratic Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 1)
  - Henrico County Democratic Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 2)
  - Hunter Mill District Democratic Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 2)
  - Loudoun Democratic Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 2)
  - Lynchburg Democratic Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 2)
  - Montgomery County Democratic Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 2)
  - Newport News Democratic Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 2)
  - Norfolk City Democratic Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 2)
  - Portsmouth of Virginia PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 2)
  - Portsmouth Democratic Women Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 2)
  - Prince William County Democratic Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 2)
  - Richmond City Democratic Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 2)
  - Rockingham County Democratic Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 2)
  - Virginia Young Democrats, 2003-2007 (Box 2)
  - Virginia Beach Democratic Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 2)
  - 1st Congressional District Republican Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 2)
  - 4th Congressional District Republican Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 2)
  - 6th Congressional District Republican Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 2)
  - 7th District Republican Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 2)
  - 8th Congressional District Republican Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 2)
  - 9th District Republican Party, 2003-2007 (Box 2)
  - 10th Congressional District Republican Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 2)
  - 11th Congressional District Republican Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 2)
  - 28th Virginia Senate District Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 2)
  - Republican Party of Virginia, Inc., 2003-2007 (Box 2)
  - Joint Republican Caucus of the Virginia General Assembly, Inc., 2003-2007 (Box 2)
  - House Republican Campaign Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 2)
  - Albemarle County Republican Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 2)
  - Alexandria Republican City Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 2)
  - Arlington County Republican Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 2)
  - Charlottesville Republican Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 2)
  - Chesterfield County Republican Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 2)
  - Fairfax Couonty Republican Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 3)
  - Fauquier County Republican Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 3)
  - Hanover County Republican Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 3)
  - Henrico County Republcian Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 3)
  - James City County Republican Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 3)
  - Log Cabin Republicans of Virginia PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 3)
  - Loudoun County Republican Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 3)
  - Montgomery County Republican Unit Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 3)
  - Newport News Republican City Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 3)
  - Northern Virginia Republican PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 3)
  - Portsmouth Republican Party City Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 3)
  - Prince William County Republican Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 3)
  - Republican Party of Chesapeake, 2003-2007 (Box 3)
  - Republican Party of Hampton City Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 3)
  - Republican Party of Norfolk, Inc., 2003-2007 (Box 3)
  - Republican Party of Virginia Beach City Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 3)
  - Republican Senate Victory PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 3)
  - Richmond Republican Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 3)
  - Spotsylvania Republican Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 3)
  - Virginia Beach Republican Senatorial Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 3)
  - 32nd House Legislative District Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 4)
  - 33rd Republican Senate Legislative District Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 4)
  - 36th District Republican Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 4)
  - 38th Newsletter Fund, 2003-2007 (Box 4)
  - The 1828 Club, 2003-2007 (Box 4)
  - Accountants Society of Virginia PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 4)
  - ActBlue Virginia, 2003-2007 (Box 4)
  - Affordable Shelter PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 4)
  - Alexandria Pro-Life Caucus, 2003-2007 (Box 4)
  - Albemarle PAC for Education, 2003-2007 (Box 4)
  - ALEX PAC (Alexandrians for Leadership and Experience PAC), 2003-2007 (Box 4)
  - Alexandria Chamber of Commerce PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 4)
  - Alexandria PAC for Education, 2003-2007 (Box 4)
  - Alexandria Young Democrats, 2003-2007 (Box 4)
  - Alexandrians for a 3% Compromise, 2003-2007 (Box 4)
  - Alexandrians for Sensible Growth, Inc., 2003-2007 (Box 4)
  - All Children Matter Virginia State PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 4)
  - All First Financial Inc. State PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 4)
  - Allegheny Education Association PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 4)
  - Allegheny Energy Federal PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 4)
  - Allstate Insurance Company PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 4)
  - Amazon.com Holdings, Inc. Separate Segregated Fund, 2003-2007 (Box 4)
  - America Coming Together (ACT VA), 2003-2007 (Box 4)
  - Amnerican Council of Engineers, 2003-2007 (Box 4)
  - American Council of Enginerring, 2003-2007 (Box 4)
  - American Council of Life Insurers, 2003-2007 (Box 4)
  - American Electric Power Committee for Responsible Government, 2003-2007 (Box 4)
  - American Hospital Association PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 4)
  - American Society of Association Executives Greater Washington, 2003-2007 (Box 4)
  - American Spirit Fund, 2003-2007 (Box 4)
  - Americans for Immigration Reform, 2003-2007 (Box 4)
  - Americans for a Republican Majority State Fund, 2003-2007 (Box 4)
  - Americans Tired of Law Suit Abuse, 2003-2007 (Box 4)
  - Anthem Health Plans of Virginia PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 4)
  - ARAMARK PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 5)
  - Arlington PAC of the Arlington Education Association, 2003-2007 (Box 5)
  - Arlington School Bonds, 2003-2007 (Box 5)
  - Arlington Young Democrats, 2003-2007 (Box 5)
  - Ashland VA PAC (A-PAC), 2003-2007 (Box 5)
  - Asian American Action Fund VA, 2003-2007 (Box 5)
  - Associated Builders and Contractors PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 5)
  - Associated General Contractors of Virginia, 2003-2007 (Box 5)
  - ATT PAC Virginia, 2003-2007 (Box 5)
  - Bank of America Virginia PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 5)
  - Bank of America State and Federal PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 5)
  - Better Government in Portsmouth, 2003-2007 (Box 5)
  - Better Government through an Informed Electorate, 2003-2007 (Box 5)
  - BIKE PAC of Virginia, 2003-2007 (Box 5)
  - Blue Dog PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 5)
  - Blue Ridge PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 5)
  - BP Corporation North America, 2003-2007 (Box 5)
  - Branch Bank and Trust of Virginia, 2003-2007 (Box 5)
  - Brian Wishneff and Sherman Lea for City Council, 2003-2007 (Box 5)
  - Buckingham Good Government League, 2003-2007 (Box 5)
  - Business Supporting Minority Candidates (BSMC), 2003-2007 (Box 5)
  - Campaign for Virginia's Families, 2003-2007 (Box 6)
  - Campaign for Working Families, 2003-2007 (Box 6)
  - Carefirst Associates PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 6)
  - Carpenters Legislative Improvement Committee United Brother, 2003-2007 (Box 6)
  - Career Schools PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 6)
  - Catalist Virginia PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 6)
  - CBC Campaign, 2003-2007 (Box 6)
  - Central Virginia Service PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 6)
  - Certified Public Accountants PAC Virginia, 2003-2007 (Box 6)
  - CHANGE, 2003-2007 (Box 6)
  - Charlottesville PAC for Education, 2003-2007 (Box 6)
  - Chesapeake Democratic Elected Officials, 2003-2007 (Box 6)
  - Chesapeake Education Association PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 6)
  - Chesapeake Republican Leadership, 2003-2007 (Box 6)
  - Chesterfield Education Association PAc, 2003-2007 (Box 6)
  - Chesterfield Forward, 2003-2007 (Box 6)
  - Chevy Chase Bank Federal PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 6)
  - Chevy Chase Bank FSB Virginia PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 6)
  - Choose Life Virginia, 2003-2007 (Box 6)
  - Cingular Wireless LLC Employees PAC Federal Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 6)
  - Cingular Wireless Employees PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 6)
  - Citigroup Inc. PAC Federal-State Virginia, 2003-2007 (Box 6)
  - Citizen Coalition on Voter Participation, 2003-2007 (Box 6)
  - Citizen Committee for Common Sense Government in Staunton, 2003-2007 (Box 6)
  - Citizens Alert, 2003-2007 (Box 6)
  - Citizens and Taxpayers PAC Virginia (Box 6)
  - Citizens for a Better Dinwiddie, 2003-2007 (Box 6)
  - Citizens for a Better Portsmouth, 2003-2007 (Box 6)
  - Citizens for an Elected School Board, 2003-2007 (Box 6)
  - Citizens for Henrico's Children, 2003-2007 (Box 6)
  - Citizens for Improving Portsmouth Schools, 2003-2007 (Box 6)
  - Citizens for the Common Good, 2003-2007 (Box 6)
  - Citizens for Common Sense and Leadership, 2003-2007 (Box 6)
  - Citizens Community Caucus, 2003-2007 (Box 6)
  - Citizens for a Quality Education, 2003-2007 (Box 6)
  - Citizens for Responsible and Balanced Growth, Inc., 2003-2007 (Box 6)
  - Citizens for a Sensible Stadium Decision, 2003-2007 (Box 6)
  - Citizens First for Blacksburg, 2003-2007 (Box 6)
  - Citizens for the Future of Frederick County, 2003-2007 (Box 6)
  - Citizens Projects PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 6)
  - Citizens Watch Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 6)
  - City Hall for All, 2003-2007 (Box 6)
  - Steve Clark for Mayor, 2003-2007 (Box 7)
  - Class of 2001 Sorenson PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 7)
  - Class of 2002 Southside Leadership Fund, 2003-2007 (Box 7)
  - Coalition Against the Tax Referendum, Inc., 2003-2007 (Box 7)
  - Coalition for a Better Richmond, 2003-2007 (Box 7)
  - Coalition for Sensible Growth, 2003-2007 (Box 7)
  - Colonial Area Republican Mens Association, 2003-2007 (Box 7)
  - Colonial Downs LP, 2003-2007 (Box 7)
  - Colonial Educators PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 7)
  - Commercial Development PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 7)
  - Commissioners and Treasurers Association of Virginia, 2003-2007 (Box 7)
  - Committee for a Better Virginia Beach, 2003-2007 (Box 7)
  - Committee for Common Sense in Staunton Governance, 2003-2007 (Box 7)
  - Committee for Economic Progress for Carroll County, 2003-2007 (Box 7)
  - Committee for Effective Government - Virginia Natural Gas, 2003-2007 (Box 7)
  - Committee for Effective Leadership (Danville, VA), 2003-2007 (Box 7)
  - Committee to Elect Tazewell County Democratic Constiutional Offices, 2003-2007 (Box 7)
  - Committee for Honest Government, 2003-2007 (Box 7)
  - Committee for Local Fiscal Integrity Responsibility and Education, 2003-2007 (Box 7)
  - Committee for Fiscal Responsibility PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 7)
  - Committee for Leadership and Progress Virginia, 2003-2007 (Box 7)
  - Committee for Quality Education, 2003-2007 (Box 7)
  - Committee for Republican Leadership, 2003-2007 (Box 7)
  - Committee for Responsible Advertising, 2003-2007 (Box 7)
  - Committee for Sound Government in the New Millenium, 2003-2007 (Box 7)
  - Committee to Elect Bauserman Burdick Pate and Rezba, 2003-2007 (Box 7)
  - Committee to Elect Frank Driscoll, 2003-2007 (Box 7)
  - Committee to Stop the New Tax on Meals and Food, 2003-2007 (Box 7)
  - Common Cents PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 7)
  - Common Sense Coalition, 2003-2007 (Box 7)
  - Common Sense for the Valley, 2003-2007 (Box 7)
  - Commonwealth Council PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 7)
  - Commonwealth Majority Fund, 2003-2007 (Box 7)
  - Community Pride Fund PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 7)
  - Council for Certified Virginia Interior Designers PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 7)
  - Commonwealth Sportsmen Alliance, 2003-2007 (Box 7)
  - Commonwealth UniServ Unit 1, 2003-2007 (Box 7)
  - Communication Workers of America COPE VA, 2003-2007 (Box 7)
  - Competitive Telecommunications Association PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 7)
  - Concerned Citizens for Political Education, 2003-2007 (Box 7)
  - Concerned Group for the Future and Quality of Life in Harrisonburg, 2003-2007 (Box 7)
  - Conservation Voters of Virginia Beach, 2003-2007 (Box 7)
  - Conservatives for Managed Growth, 2003-2007 (Box 7)
  - Constitution Party of Virginia, 2003-2007 (Box 7)
  - Covington PAC for Education, 2003-2007 (Box 7)
  - CRIS PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 7)
  - Curtiss Wright Corporation Employee PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 7)
  - CVS Corporation Federal PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 7)
  - D4D PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 7)
  - Democracy for America VA, 2003-2007 (Box 7)
  - Deere and Company PAC Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 7)
  - Dedicated Americans for the Senate and House PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 7)
  - Dell Inc. Employee PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 8)
  - Democracy for Virginia PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 8)
  - Democracy Prevails, 2003-2007 (Box 8)
  - Democratic Latino Organization of Virginia, 2003-2007 (Box 8)
  - Democratic Club of Virginia PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 8)
  - Democratic Governors Association-Virginia, 2003-2007 (Box 8)
  - Democratic Lt. Governors Association, 2003-2007 (Box 8)
  - Democratic National Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 8)
  - Democratic Road Back PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 8)
  - Democrats for Scott York, 2003-2007 (Box 8)
  - Dental Hygienists for Northern Virginia, 2003-2007 (Box 8)
  - Diamler Chrysler Corporation PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 8)
  - DLA Piper Rudnick Gray US LLP PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 8)
  - Dominion Leadership Trust PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 8)
  - Dominion PAC Virginia, 2003-2007 (Box 8)
  - Dominion UniServ Educators PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 8)
  - Downtown Republican Club, Inc., 2003-2007 (Box 8)
  - Don't Stop Thinking About Tomorrow PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 8)
  - D.R.I.V.E. - Democrat Republican Independent Voter Education, 2003-2007 (Box 8)
  - Duke Energy Corporation PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 8)
  - Dynamic Leadership PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 8)
  - EAN PACE, 2003-2007 (Box 8)
  - Eckerd Corporation PAC (1 of 2) (Box 8)
  - Eckerd Corporation PAC (2 of 2) (Box 8)
  - EDS Employees PAC (Box 8)
  - Ed-U-Serv (Box 8)
  - Eli Lilly and Company PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 8)
  - Embarq Corporation Employees PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 8)
  - Emergency Medicine PAC of Virginia, 2003-2007 (Box 8)
  - Emily's List Virginia, 2003-2007 (Box 8)
  - Enterprise Rent-A-Car Company PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 8)
  - EPIC PharmPAC of Virginia, 2003-2007 (Box 8)
  - Equitable Resources Inc. Political Involvement Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 8)
  - Euille PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 8)
  - EYE PAC-Virginia Opthalmology, 2003-2007 (Box 8)
  - Fairfax Citizens for Better Schools, 2003-2007 (Box 9)
  - Fairfax County Chamber of Commerce, 2003-2007 (Box 9)
  - Fairfax County Citizens for School Bond, 2003-2007 (Box 9)
  - Fairfax County Federation of Teachers Committee on Political Education, 2003-2007 (Box 9)
  - Fairfax County PAC for Educators, 2003-2007 (Box 9)
  - Fairfax Deputy PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 9)
  - Family Farmers of Virginia PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 9)
  - Family Therapists for Virginia's Families, 2003-2007 (Box 9)
  - Fauquier Alliance for Better Schools, 2003-2007 (Box 9)
  - Fauquier Education Association PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 9)
  - Federal Victory Fund, 2003-2007 (Box 9)
  - Ferguson Victory Fund, 2003-2007 (Box 9)
  - Ferguson Tejada for County Board, 2003-2007 (Box 9)
  - Filipino American Republicans of Virginia, Inc., 2003-2007 (Box 9)
  - FirePAC Local 2068, 2003-2007 (Box 9)
  - First Citizens Bankshares, Inc. PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 9)
  - Foodservice III PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 9)
  - Ford Motor Company Civic Action Fund, 2003-2007 (Box 9)
  - Former Blackhawks for Good Government, 2003-2007 (Box 9)
  - Forward America PAC-Virginia, 2003-2007 (Box 9)
  - Forward Norfolk PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 9)
  - Forward Virginia PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 9)
  - Foster Virginia, 2003-2007 (Box 9)
  - Frederick County Voters Association PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 9)
  - Fredericksburg Area Construction Trust, 2003-2007 (Box 9)
  - Friends of Cavalier, 2003-2007 (Box 9)
  - Friends of Hamro, 2003-2007 (Box 9)
  - Friends of the Elephant, 2003-2007 (Box 9)
  - Friends of the Fifth District Republican Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 9)
  - Friends of Harry J. Parrish, 2003-2007 (Box 9)
  - Friends of Jackie Jackson, 2003-2007 (Box 9)
  - Friends of Jeff Sili, 2003-2007 (Box 9)
  - Friends of John Elledge, 2003-2007 (Box 9)
  - Friends of John Newhart, 2003-2007 (Box 9)
  - Friends of Lacey Putney, 2003-2007 (Box 9)
  - Friends of Manoli Loupassi, 2003-2007 (Box 9)
  - Friends of Mike Signer, 2003-2007 (Box 9)
  - Friends of Pataki, 2003-2007 (Box 9)
  - Friends of Pharmacy PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 9)
  - Friends of Sheriff Roger J. McCabe, 2003-2007 (Box 9)
  - Friends of Our Southern Heritage, 2003-2007 (Box 9)
  - Friends of Southside Virginia, 2003-2007 (Box 9)
  - Friends of Virginia Heritage, 2003-2007 (Box 9)
  - Friends of Will Shaw, 2003-2007 (Box 9)
  - Fund for the Future of Virginia, 2003-2007 (Box 9)
  - Fund for Virginia's Future, 2003-2007 (Box 9)
  - Future Deeds, 2003-2007 (Box 9)
  - Gateway Good Government Fund, 2003-2007 (Box 10)
  - Gay and Lesbian Victory Fund (03-090), 2003-2007 (Box 10)
  - Gay and Lesbian Victory Fund (05-004), 2003-2007 (Box 10)
  - Geico New York PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 10)
  - General Motors Corporation PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 10)
  - GILPAC, 2003-2007 (Box 10)
  - Good Government for America, 2003-2007 (Box 10)
  - Good Jobs Now, 2003-2007 (Box 10)
  - GOPAC, 2003-2007 (Box 10)
  - Grassroots Democrats, 2003-2007 (Box 10)
  - Greater Washington Board of Trade, 2003-2007 (Box 10)
  - Green Space Ladies, 2003-2007 (Box 10)
  - GrowPAC, 2003-2007 (Box 10)
  - Growing Chesterfield Business Inc. PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 10)
  - Gun Owners of America Inc. PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 10)
  - Gwen's Local List, 2003-2007 (Box 10)
  - Hampton Now, 2003-2007 (Box 10)
  - Hampton Roads Business PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 10)
  - Hampton Roads Realtor PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 10)
  - Hampton Roads Taxpayer Coalition, 2003-2007 (Box 10)
  - Hampton Roads Transportation PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 10)
  - Hampton Watch, 2003-2007 (Box 10)
  - Hanover Conservation Voters, 2003-2007 (Box 10)
  - Hanover House Leadership PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 10)
  - Hanover Taxpayers for Responsible Government, 2003-2007 (Box 10)
  - Hartford Advocates Fund (003-047), 2003-2007 (Box 10)
  - Hartford Advocates Fund (99-059), 2003-2007 (Box 10)
  - HBAR Build PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 10)
  - HBAV Build PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 10)
  - HCA for Good Government, 2003-2007 (Box 10)
  - Heavy Construction Contractors Association PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 10)
  - Help Save Loudoun PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 10)
  - Henrico PAC for Education, 2003-2007 (Box 10)
  - Hester McDonald Golf Classic '04, 2003-2007 (Box 10)
  - Holtzman Vogel PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 10)
  - Home School Legal Defense PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 10)
  - Honest Reform PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 10)
  - Honeywell Virginia PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 10)
  - Hoosier PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 10)
  - Hope for America PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 10)
  - HSBC North America PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 10)
  - HRUHCA, 2003-2007 (Box 10)
  - IFAPAC, 2003-2007 (Box 11)
  - INDEPAC, 2003-2007 (Box 11)
  - INGENCO PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 11)
  - International Longshoremen, 2003-2007 (Box 11)
  - International Paper PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 11)
  - International Union of Elevator Constructors Local No. 10 PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 11)